{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Rendering in React",
      "description": "React's component structure allows for quickly building a complex web application that relies on DOM manipulation. "
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application."
    },
    {
      "name": "Mario",
      "description": "Luigi",
      "id": 4
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?\n<Route>\n  <NotFound />\n</Route>",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all URL's",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "front": "putting deletes",
      "back": "how come"
    },
    {
      "front": "Can I add a card?",
      "back": "yes",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "Add a card",
      "back": "Ok",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "Three cards",
      "back": "ok",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "front": "brah",
      "back": "dude",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "front": "New card",
      "back": "please",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "front": "asdfasdf",
      "back": "asdfasdfdsf",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "front": "hoody hoo",
      "back": "try",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "front": "qwerty",
      "back": "qwerty",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "front": "RDRRRR",
      "back": "argh",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 20
    }
  ]
}